[{
        "question": "What is 6 ÷ 2?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 15 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 20 ÷ 4?",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 24 ÷ 6?",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 21 ÷ 7?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 12 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 18 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 9 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 27 ÷ 9?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 35 ÷ 7?",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 14 ÷ 2?",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 8 ÷ 4?",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 25 ÷ 5?",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 36 ÷ 6?",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 32 ÷ 8?",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 40 ÷ 5?",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 28 ÷ 4?",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 45 ÷ 9?",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 30 ÷ 10?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]